altredo.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Altredo

We take your privacy seriously the interaction with clients at Altredo is based on principles of confidentiality. This privacy statement discloses the type of information we gather and to create secure operating conditions. 

Collected Information   
We collected personal information on its clients such as your name, email address postal address (for developers only), phone number and credit card number in order to provide them the best services. 

Using Your Personal Information   
Your personal information is protected and not given out to anyone or used by us other than a purchase.

Methods of Payment   
As a registered subscriber, you will have full access to our Predictive Analytics Software (download or subscription versions). To make payments, you can use accepted payment methods (see on our web-site www.altredo.com), as a registered user, your account will be activated immediately and you will receive full access to our software.

Cancellation Policy   
If you decide that our product is not the right product for you, you can cancel your subscription through contact us. Your cancellation request will be effective at the end of your current subscription period. All monthly payments are FINAL. No refunds offered for period based subscription! Altredo reserves the right to cancel any unpaid account without notice.

Our cookies Policy   
Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.

Privacy policy changes   
Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this area of this Web site. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our sites that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy statement.
